EPISODE 5: PRISONER OF LOVE
What's this?
Looks like you're awake.
Were we dreaming just now?
Yes. And this substance is dissolving us.
In this very room.
Please break down the door…
Use your ability, Star Platinum.
Hurry!
You did it! Now drag me out!
Let's get out of here!
Hold on.
What did you just say?
Did you say "Star Platinum"?
That's my Stand name.
How do you know that, Jolyne?
From the looks of it,
we started dreaming
after I told you about Johngalli A.
Which means
you haven't seen my Stand ability yet.
Since we are related,
you may be feeling its presence,
but you couldn't have known its name.
It's not adding up!
This is
not reality!
Stone Ocean…
Jolyne.
You finally woke up.
That took too much effort.
My thread melts fast.
Jolyne… You were dreaming too.
I don't know about yours,
but mine was a terrible nightmare.
I see.
So we were both dreaming
as if watching a movie.
Guess so. It would've been perfect
if only we had some popcorn.
I can't move anymore. Not even a finger.
What about you? Can you move?
What we are perceiving
could still be a dream.
If you can't move at all,
then we're awake.
We are in this reality
where we can't escape this room.
I see.
We'll die at this rate.
The charm's ability…
Show me the ability you used
to wake me up.
Stone Ocean.
Yes. Can you materialize it?
I mean your power.
I understand, but it's no use.
It was hard enough to wake you up.
No way could I break down the door.
No, just materialize it.
That's it.
Keep going.
Can you bring it out a bit more?
Move it slightly towards me.
It'd be best if you could move it
a bit more to the left.
This will do.
It's not ideal, but it's close enough.
Now we can leave this room.
That was my Stand, "Star Platinum."
Pull me out. This isn't a dream.
I'm certain of it now.
Damn you…
Bullshit…
It hurts and I'm pissed.
I can't believe you hit me.
We got out, but I'm pissed!
We're definitely not dreaming, all right!
Okay, give me your hands.
What now?
Let's go.
Oh, right.
Do you know what this is?
This bone saved our lives.
It's a human bone.
Plus,
it's the sacrum from
the pelvic area of an adult female.
Its surface looks like
it was dissolved with some kind of acid.
Dissolved?
Is that what was used on us?
Can't say.
I don't know why you have that bone,
but it doesn't matter now.
I was the only one who saw that boy,
but he's definitely here!
It's a mystery,
but he's within these prison walls!
Code 909, emergency level 4.
Emergency alarm activated
in the visitation room.
Emergency level 4, code 909.
What's your plan now?
I guess now you're a criminal too.
Like I told you,
I'm breaking you out.
You have the charm, don't you?
It's crucial that you hold onto it.
Don't lose it, no matter what.
Let's go. We're leaving this place.
Who would have thought that
they would be able to escape this room.
Is it just me?
I don't see that many guards.
This is a common area.
Look at this.
We'll escape through the window
marked with an X.
This window faces the beach.
We'll board a submarine at the beach
to escape this island.
A submarine?
I have an amicable relationship
with a group
called The Speedwagon Foundation.
They have provided our way out.
There doesn't seem to be
a camera in this hallway.
Our target window is one left turn away.
Then we'll be about 20m
away from the shore.
I'm sure there is a lot to consider,
but let's get out of here first.
Let's go.
It's just the fan.
Jolyne.
It hurts!
Where are you looking? Stay calm.
Stand up.
What's the matter? Give me your hand.
It's just that…
Well, thanks,
but I can stand up by myself.
That's not what I meant.
You almost lost this.
Be careful when you trip.
I told you not to lose this charm.
What is it?
I told you it's important.
You must hold onto it. Take it.
You're headed to Tokyo?
This is your daughter we're talking about!
And you call yourself her father?
Hello? Are you there?
You haven't changed a bit.
You're calm and collected as ever.
When I almost died from a fever,
you didn't come home to check on me.
When I drove a car for fun
and was accused of theft,
you took a plane to Tokyo instead.
Right. As long as I'm safe,
you don't care, do you?
Even now, I'm just a troublemaker
that doesn't get hurt even if I fall! See?
Lucky me, no harm done! Yahoo!
What are you talking about?
If it's that important, hold it yourself!
Listen.
Shut up. I don't want it!
That's not it. Something is off.
We're being quietly followed.
Jolyne, duck.
There's no one over here.
They might have headed the other way.
Oh, it's just a guard.
Hey, look closely!
The door is bent!
The convicts have come this far!
We are at--
That's…
Johngalli A.!
That bastard…
He's here to finish us off himself!
Jolyne! Head towards the window.
I'll take care of him.
That's Johngalli A.'s Stand!
But the only time
he ambushed us was in a dream.
-Die!
-Are we still dreaming?
No! This is reality!
Time stop!
Our enemies…
There are…
two of them!
Not only did he force us to dream,
but he showed us
Johngalli A.'s actual Stand within it!
They had been preparing for this moment.
The moment
I have no choice
but to use my Stand ability
to protect my daughter!
Their target
was me all along!
Time will move again. Jolyne!
You were one move behind.
Jotaro Kujo, I have been waiting
for this moment!
It was just ready for me.
Perfect.
I finally got what I've been after
from Jotaro, the invincible Stand User!
This is Pale Snake's ability!
Those bullets!
The Stand!
How?
I thought we only saw
his Stand in our dream!
Anyway, while he can't shoot, I'll…
I see the shore! We're close!
Go on without me.
I'll catch up.
Were you actually…
shot?
Listen to me.
A Stand User only controls one Stand.
This means we are up against two enemies,
Johngalli A. and the one
who tried to dissolve us.
Go on ahead.
Take this charm.
Don't drop it.
A transmitter is implanted within it.
It's there to track your location.
The submarine is honed
to follow the GPS signal.
You understand what I'm saying, right?
All you have to do is go to the beach.
The submarine will come to you.
And The Speedwagon Foundation
I told you about will find you.
If you understand, then go, Jolyne.
This charm…
But earlier, you…
No. You couldn't have…
I've always cared about you.
What is it?
Your chest… You're not…
No, why?
Go, Jolyne.
It's just a little blood.
I'll catch up soon.
Liar!
Earlier, you sacrificed yourself,
and the enemy took something from you!
That's why you couldn't
evade the bullets, right?
What did he take?
Don't tell me… your Stand?
Jolyne!
What?
These are…
These threads!
Since when?
Take this!
Shut up.
We're about to leave from this window
and head for the beach.
Don't get in our way. Got that?
You…
When did she acquire such a Stand ability?
An ability of this strength
should have been reported
before her sentencing!
Very well. I will drop my gun.
I wasn't asking you to drop your gun.
I was just looking for the best angle.
Your body's best angle to punch, that is.
I only like it when your chin
is tilted slightly to the right.
Just now,
I should have finished her first
instead of Jotaro!
Jotaro wasn't the one
I should've gone for first.
Does Pale Snake know about this?
Jolyne Cujoh.
Without a doubt, she is Jotaro Kujo's…
She's a Joestar!
Jolyne.
Back then, in that dream…
you said you'll stay behind at this jail
for some child you barely just met.
He grabbed my arm
with desperation in his eyes.
I'm going back inside.
It was a mere dream I saw.
But…
Dad!
Dammit, we're so close to the beach!
Find them! We have permission to shoot!
A guard has been shot.
The convict is armed.
We can shoot to kill!
Where is it? I'm at the beach already.
Where are they?
That organization you're friends with,
called The Speedwagon Foundation…
I don't know who they are,
but if they really did send us
a submarine,
then they must have incredibly
advanced technology and financial power!
A gunshot wound like this…
This foundation must be able to administer
the care you need better than anyone else!
Where is the submarine?
Where is it?
Everything you said was true.
The submarine is already at the beach!
We're saved…
What the hell are you doing?
You can't…
No, this can't be happening.
No, this isn't happening.
He was shot, but it wasn't deep.
It's not a fatal wound.
It can't be a fatal wound.
Then,
Then his heart…
Why isn't it beating?
Now, I know.
The Joestar blood runs in you.
Jolyne, with your strong conviction,
I know you'll be fine.
Found them!
Something's moving
on the other side of the fence!
Watch for the gun!
No, I'm not outside the fence.
I'm right here
if you're looking for me.
You!
Hold, don't shoot!
Her hands are up.
-But…
-Don't shoot!
She's unarmed.
Are you surrendering?
There must be another man.
A tall man who visited her.
He must be nearby. Find him!
That's where you were.
Why?
Why didn't you run?
I'm sorry,
but your father is already dead.
His spirit was stolen by that sludge.
You barely managed to survive!
Why didn't you leave? Why?
The murderer escaped inside the prison.
Not outside, inside!
The murderer had planned to steal
my father's Stand by giving it form.
That's his ability!
Then the murderer retreated
back into the prison.
He won't leave this place.
He is within these walls!
Are you actually trying
to get his ability back?
Do you think it'll bring him back to life?
That's precisely why
I'm going back inside.
I'm sorry to say this,
but a corpse will only rot away.
That melted bone I gave you
belonged to my mother.
That sludge stole her ability
and she died.
I see.
My mom was an inmate here
and gave birth to me.
I grew up in hiding within these walls.
What's your name?
I'm Emporio.
Emporio.
Your mother's bone saved my life.
Thank you.
But,
I can't explain it, but I'm certain of it.
My dad's not dead.
If I get his Stand back,
he will come back to life.
That's why
I'm going back!
You've done it.
You finally acquired
this powerful Stand which can stop time!
Yes, and I have you to thank, Johngalli A.
We make a great team together.
Please take me to the men's prison.
I let my guard down.
And have you seen my gun?
It's right here.
You're the only one who knows who I am.
You shall be my scapegoat
for the murder of the guards.
This way, everything works out peacefully.
To be able to communicate
something to someone...
Jotaro had said that is a wonderful thing.
I agree.
And here, we have a way.
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter